{
    "subject": "resource/Arthur_Conan_Doyle",
    "predicate": "ontology/notableWork",
    "object": "resource/Canon_of_Sherlock_Holmes",
    "human_readable": "Arthur Conan Doyle is notable for 'Canon of Sherlock Holmes'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.751483142375946,
            "question": "Name some works by Arthur Conan Doyle featuring Sherlock Holmes."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7485960125923157,
            "question": "Who is Arthur Conan Doyle known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7428759932518005,
            "question": "What is the Canon of Sherlock Holmes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5488465428352356,
            "question": "What literary creations is Arthur Conan Doyle famous for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5114737153053284,
            "question": "What impact has the Canon of Sherlock Holmes had on popular culture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44307902455329895,
            "question": "Besides Sherlock Holmes, what other characters did Arthur Conan Doyle create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32121220231056213,
            "question": "Why is Arthur Conan Doyle considered a significant author?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3165936768054962,
            "question": "What makes Sherlock Holmes such a compelling character?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29121002554893494,
            "question": "What genre of literature is associated with Arthur Conan Doyle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.236348956823349,
            "question": "How did Arthur Conan Doyle's writing influence detective fiction?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Arthur Conan Doyle is notable for 'Canon of Sherlock Holmes'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8020_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of literature is associated with Arthur Conan Doyle?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8020_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes Sherlock Holmes such a compelling character?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8020_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why is Arthur Conan Doyle considered a significant author?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8020_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8020_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8020_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8020_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8020_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8020_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8020_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8020_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8020_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8020_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8020_59.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information supporting that Arthur Conan Doyle is notably associated with the \"Canon of Sherlock Holmes,\" which includes his famous series and short stories featuring Sherlock Holmes."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}